kibagames.com 2014-11-23

# Games for Kids, Girls & Boys - Free Online Games at KibaGames.com

**1\. Information on data protection**

Protecting your data has highest priority. We compile user data in accordance with the currently applicable data protection laws and use this data among other things to improve our advertising campaigns. Especially in relation to our younger users, we take special care to ensure the responsible use of the data. We have set out our data protection policy to show you that you and your children can use our free website without risk.

Please never enter your personal data, such as your e-mail address, telephone number or passwords, etc., on public domains and never give this information to other users either. Our support team and other staff will also never ask you for personal data.

**2\. Scope**

This Privacy Policy explains the type, scope and purposes of data collection and the use of personal data by the responsible provider KaiserGames GmbH, Schanzenstraße 6-20, D-51063 Cologne, info@kibagames.com, +49 221 7880610on this site (hereinafter called “website”).

This Privacy Policy applies to all services offered by the provider. Unless otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy exclusively governs how the provider handles your personal data. If you use third party services, only the data protection policies for these third parties apply. The provider does not check the data protection policies of third parties.

**3\. Data collection**

Generally, you can access our website without disclosing any personal data. You are always free to decide whether you would like to communicate your data to us or not. We collect your data tofulfillthe user contract agreed with you. This includes monitoring adherence to the user conditions and rules of play.If you register on our website or would like to subscribe to our newsletter, you will need to provide personal data, such as your name, your address, your e-mail address and other personal data that we may request. In addition, individual data such as your IP address, browser type and access pages are automatically transmitted to us through your computer and stored on our server. Apart from the purpose of monitoring illegal access to our internet services, we only use this data for statistical analysis and performance-related purposes. Where possible, the data is anonymized.

Like many other companies, we use so-called "cookies" to make your visit to our website as pleasant as possible. These cookies are generally automatically deleted from your hard disk when they are no longer valid. You can set your internet browser to generally decline cookies. Please note that for technical reasons, you may no longer be able to use our website or your use may be restricted. We may also receive information from social network systems on which you use our website or if you have logged in through their interface (e.g. Facebook Connect). We only collect, process, and use personal data and data provided by you - unless already permitted by legal authorization -with your consent. If your consent is provided electronically within the scope of our website, we comply with statutory obligations to provide information.

Our website uses the Gemius Code (http://www.iabeurope.eu/corporate-members/gemius.aspx) from IAB Turkey (http://www.iabeurope.eu/national-iabs/turkey.aspx) to compile statistical parameters on the use of our website. The values are anonymized. The Gemius audience reach measurement method recognizes computer systems by either a cookie or a signature generated from various information automatically transmitted from your computer. This method does not store IP addresses; these are processed in an anonymized form only. The audience reach measurement method was developed in accordance with the data protection regulations and its objective is to statistically determine the intensity of use and the number of users of a particular website. Specific users are not identified at any stage. Your identity always remains protected. You will not receive any advertisements via the system.

**4\. Use of data**

We use information about you to tailor and continuously improve our services to meet your requirements. We use your personal details to establish, maintain, and conclude your business relationship with us. We also use your data to communicate with you. This may include e-mailing you about our latest services. We use your data to regularly inform you about products, services and selected events on our website that may be of interest to you. You may also receive customer questionnaires by e-mail from us. The information we provide will point out how you can opt out of this. Finally, we use your data to prevent misuse of our website and to track unauthorized access.

**5\. Disclosure of data**

We will, of course, not sell your personal data to third parties. We will only disclose the personal data you provide in the follow scenarios: We cooperate with providers that create, compile and analyze statistical data, IT service providers, (e.g. data centers, hosts, backup services, database services, e-mail services, support providers) and advertising agencies. These service providers only have access to your personal data to the extent which is necessary for the completion of their tasks. These service providers are obliged to treat your personal data as specified in this Privacy Policy and the relevant data protection statutes. In the event that we, companies we control, particular individual subsidiaries or sections of the company are sold, your customer data will generally be passed on with the transferred part of the company. Of course, in this case your data is also subject to this Privacy Policy and the relevant data protection statutes.

**6\. Deletion of data**

If your data is no longer necessary for the above-mentioned purposes including settlement, for tax purposes or other legal reasons, it will be deleted.

**7\. Data security**

We process the data collected from you according to the German Data Protection Act. All employees are obliged and have been advised to maintain data confidentiality and privacy obligations.

**8\. Facebook Social Plugins**

This website uses SocialPlugins("Plugins") provided by the social network facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins can be identified by the Facebook logos (white "f" on a blue background or a "thumbs up" icon) or the extension “Facebook Social Plugin” (<http://developers.facebook.com/plugins>).

When a user visits a page of website that contains a social plugin, the browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website. We accordingly have no influence over the scope of the data that Facebook acquires using this plugin and therefore draw your attention to the information we have available in this respect (<http://www.facebook.com/help/?faq=17512>).

The embedded plugins let Facebook know that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking “Like”, or entering a comment, your browser will send the corresponding information directly to Facebook, at which point it will be saved. If you are not a member of Facebook, Facebook may still acquire and store your IP address. Facebook ensures that, in Germany, the IP address will only be stored anonymously.

For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and handling by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and configuration options regarding the protection of your personal sphere, please visit Facebook's data use policy (<http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>).

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to collect data concerning your visit to our website and do not want this linked to your Facebook membership data, please log out of Facebook before visiting our website.

You can also block Facebook Social Plugins by using add-ons for your browser, such as “Facebook Blocker” (<http://webgraph.com/resources/facebookblocker>).

**9\. Twitter**

This website uses the service functions for Twitter (<https://twitter.com/about/resources/buttons>). These functions are provided by Twitter, Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA, and can be identified by terms such as “Twitter” or “Tweet” combined with a stylized blue bird. A Twitter button enables you to either share a posting or page of this website on Twitter or to follow us on Twitter.

When a user visits a page of website that contains this plugin, the browser establishes a direct connection to Twitter servers. Twitter directly transfers the Twitter button contents to your browser. Thus, we have no influence on the data acquired by Twitter using the plugin and therefore draw your attention to the information we have available in this respect. According to Twitter, only the user's IP address and the URL of the relevant website in connection with the button are transmitted and only used for the purposes represented by the button. For further information, please follow this link to Twitter's privacy policy (<http://twitter.com/privacy>).

**10\. Google Plus**

This website uses the “+1″button of the social network Google Plus, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"). The button can be identified by the “+1″on a white or colored background.

When you access a page of the website that contains one of these buttons, your browser establishes a direct connection with Google's servers. The content of the “+1″button is transmitted directly to your browser by Google and incorporated by the browser into the website. We therefore have no influence on the scope of the data that Google collects via this button. According to Google, no personal data is collected unless the user clicks on the button. This data, such as the IP address, is only collected and processed from logged-in members.

The purpose and extent of the data collection and the further handling and usage of the data by Google, as well as the rights and possible settings to protect the privacy of the user, are outlined in Google's privacy policy on the “+1″-button (<http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html>) and the FAQ ([http://support.google.com/plus/bin/answer.py?hl=de&answer=1319578&rd=1](http://support.google.com/plus/bin/answer.py?hl=de&answer=1319578&rd=1)).

If you are a member of Google Plus and do not want Google to be able to collect personal information through our website and link it to your Google membership data, you must log out of Google Plus before visiting our website.

**11\. Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how you use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be generally transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the USA.

If the IP anonymizer is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the whole IP address be transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there. The IP anonymizer is activated on this website. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing them with other services relating to website activity and internet usage.

Google will never link your IP address sent by your browser to other Google data. You can configure your browser software to block the installation of cookies on your computer; however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also prevent the data generated by the cookie which relates to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) from being recorded at Google, as well as the handling of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link (<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de>).

**12\. Revocation, amendments, revisions and updates**

You have the right to receive information free-of-charge on the personal data held on you. You also have the right to rectify inaccurate data and to block and erase personal data, provided this is not in breach of any statutory duty to preserve records.

Source: Schwenke Attorney at Law (<http://rechtsanwalt-schwenke.de/smmr-buch/datenschutz-muster-generator-fuer-webseiten-blogs-und-social-media/>)
